Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
(Prince Regent's Mansion)
(قصر الأمير ريجنت)
(Shen Yuqing, Daughter of the Duke's concubine) Shen Yuqing.
(شين يو تشينغ، ابنة محظية الدوق) شين يو تشينغ.
(Shen Yuanjin, Daughter of the Duke's wife) You, a mute concubine-born daughter,
(شين يوانجين، ابنة زوجة الدوق) أنت، ابنة خرساء ولدت من محظية،
dare claim resemblance to me?
هل تجرؤ على ادعاء الشبه بي؟
Tonight is my wedding night with Pei Ji.
الليلة هي ليلة زفافي مع باي جي.
To let you serve him is already a favor.
إن السماح لك بخدمته هو بالفعل معروف.
How dare you feel wronged?
كيف تجرؤ على الشعور بالظلم؟
The Prince Regent arrives.
يصل الأمير الوصي.
Perform convincingly later.
أداء مقنع في وقت لاحق.
Pei Ji's the Prince Regent who even scorns the Emperor.
بي جي هو الأمير الوصي الذي يحتقر حتى الإمبراطور.
If the Duke's Mansion face consequences,
إذا واجه قصر الدوق عواقب،
I'll make sure you and your mad mother die without graves.
سأتأكد من أنك وأمك المجنونة تموتان بلا قبر.
(Pei Ji, Prince Regent)
(بي جي، الأمير الوصي)
You've got some nerve,
لقد حصلت على بعض الشجاعة
daring to drug me with euphoria powder.
يجرؤ على تخديري بمسحوق النشوة.
I detest being manipulated.
أنا أكره أن يتم التلاعب بي.
I merely wished to share
لقد أردت فقط أن أشارك
an unforgettable wedding night with you.
ليلة زفاف لا تنسى معك.
(Had I remained chaste,)
(لو بقيت عفيفة)
(how could a mute concubine's daughter like you qualify?)
(كيف يمكن لابنة محظية خرساء مثلك أن تتأهل؟)
=The Maid=
=الخادمة=
=Episode 1=
=الحلقة 1=
(Three months later) You shameless woman, kneel.
(بعد ثلاثة أشهر) أيتها المرأة الوقحة، اركعي.
Kneel!
اركع!
Yuanjin, you promised
يوانجين، لقد وعدت
that after fulfilling your marital duties for you,
أنه بعد أن قمت بأداء واجباتك الزوجية تجاهك،
you'd release me and my mother.
ستطلق سراحي وأمي.
You dare hunger strike against me?
هل تجرؤ على الإضراب عن الطعام ضدي؟
Like your mother, both unfit for decent company
مثل والدتك، كلاهما غير مناسبين للشركة اللائقة
and only skilled at seducing men.
وماهرة فقط في إغواء الرجال.
Guards!
حراس!
(Qin Xiaoniang, The Duke's concubine)
(تشين شياو يانغ، خليلة الدوق)
Kneel.
اركع.
(Que'nu, Shen Yuanjin's maid)
(كينو، خادمة شين يوانجين)
Today I'll teach you to remember
اليوم سأعلمك كيف تتذكر
what it means for an ant to shake a tree.
ماذا يعني أن تهز نملة شجرة؟
You're overestimating your strength.
أنت تبالغ في تقدير قوتك.
Now, that's obedience.
الآن، هذه هي الطاعة.
If you do this again,
إذا فعلت هذا مرة أخرى،
it will pierce
سوف يخترق
through her throat.
من خلال حلقها.
Mother,
الأم،
I was wrong.
لقد كنت مخطئا.
I thought as long as we play dumb, act crazy,
اعتقدت أنه طالما أننا نلعب دور الأغبياء، ونتصرف بجنون،
and do as we're told,
ونفعل كما قيل لنا،
she would let us go.
إنها ستسمح لنا بالذهاب.
Mother.
الأم.
Qing.
تشينغ.
Your hand.
يدك.
Slippery pulse?
نبض زلق؟
Qing,
تشينغ،
you're with child?
هل انت حامل بطفل؟
No wonder she stopped assigning you chores.
لا عجب أنها توقفت عن تكليفك بالمهام المنزلية.
She plans to claim your child as hers.
إنها تخطط للمطالبة بطفلك باعتباره ابنها.
When cleaning Yuanjin's courtyard,
عند تنظيف فناء يوانجين،
I found miscarriage-treatment herbs.
لقد وجدت أعشاب لعلاج الإجهاض.
She aborted her own child, damaging her fertility.
لقد أجهضت طفلها، مما أثر على خصوبتها.
Mother,
الأم،
after this child's birth,
بعد ولادة هذا الطفل،
she'll surely silence us permanently.
إنها بالتأكيد سوف تسكتنا إلى الأبد.
Qing,
تشينغ،
your delivery
تسليمك
will be our only chance to escape.
ستكون فرصتنا الوحيدة للهروب.
(Yangque Garden)
(حديقة يانجكي)
(Seven months later)
(بعد سبعة أشهر)
The amniotic fluid broke.
انكسر السائل الأمنيوسي.
The delivery begins.
بدأ التسليم.
You stay here.
ابقى هنا.
I'll fetch the midwife.
سأحضر القابلة.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Guards!
حراس!
Mother.
الأم.
Mother, let's go.
أمي هيا بنا.
(Yangque Garden)
(حديقة يانجكي)
(Meixiang House)
(بيت ميكسيانج)
(Qing,)
(تشينغ)
(run!)
(يجري!)
(Qing.)
(تشينغ.)
(Li Si, Guard of the Duke's Mansion)
(لي سي، حارس قصر الدوق)
Retreat.
تراجع.
Live well...
عش جيدا...
(Shen Yuqing,)
(شين يو تشينغ،)
(stay awake.)
(ابقى مستيقظا.)
(Madam) Lady Qingmei truly has skills.
(السيدة) السيدة تشينغمي لديها مهارات حقيقية.
Even the self-proclaimed romantic vanguard, Prince Zhennan
حتى الطليعة الرومانسية التي أعلنت نفسها بنفسها ، الأمير جينان
succumbs to your charm.
يستسلم لسحرك.
Stop.
قف.
(Qingmei, Top courtesan at Meixiang House)
(تشينغمي، إحدى كبار المحظيات في منزل ميكسيانغ)
This is the snow-fox fur from Prince Zhennan.
هذا هو فراء الثعلب الثلجي من الأمير جينان.
Worth a fortune.
يستحق ثروة.
Mere material.
مجرد مادة.
Why value it?
لماذا نقدر ذلك؟
I don't want furs.
لا أريد فراء.
I just want
انا فقط اريد
to serve you.
لخدمتك.
(Meixiang House)
(بيت ميكسيانج)
Why learn seduction from me?
لماذا تتعلم الإغواء مني؟
I want to be like you,
أريد أن أكون مثلك
toying with powerful officials in the palm of your hand.
اللعب مع المسؤولين الأقوياء في راحة يدك.
Targeting some official?
استهداف بعض المسؤولين؟
The Prince Regent,
الأمير الوصي،
Pei Ji.
باي جي.
Interesting.
مثير للاهتمام.
Even I couldn't conquer him.
حتى أنني لم أستطع التغلب عليه.
I surpass you in one aspect.
أنا أتفوق عليك في جانب واحد.
Surpass me?
تتفوق علي؟
I have no retreat.
ليس لدي أي تراجع.
This is a scar.
هذه ندبة.
My mother made an ointment for me.
لقد صنعت لي أمي مرهمًا.
Normally invisible.
غير مرئية عادة.
Once the body becomes feverish,
بمجرد أن يصبح الجسم محموما،
it will reappear.
سوف تظهر مرة أخرى.
This means
هذا يعنى
when carnal desires arise,
عندما تنشأ الرغبات الجسدية،
it'll also emerge?
هل ستظهر أيضا؟
I'll teach you to control passions.
سأعلمك كيفية التحكم في عواطفك.
Thanks for taking me in, Master.
شكرا لاستقبالي، يا سيدي.
Mandala is also called Xiyan.
يُطلق على الماندالا أيضًا اسم Xiyan.
Remember this.
تذكر هذا.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
there's no Shen Yuqing, daughter of the Duke.
لا يوجد شين يوتشينغ، ابنة الدوق.
There's only Xiyan,
لا يوجد سوى Xiyan،
courtesan from Meixiang House.
عاهرة من منزل ميكسيانج.
(Shen Yuqing, Daughter of Duke's concubine)
(شين يو تشينغ، ابنة محظية الدوق)
(Xiyan, Courtesan from Meixiang House)
(شيان، مومس من منزل Meixiang)
Come on.
تعال.
Good!
جيد!
Wonderful!
رائع!
I'll help you
سأساعدك
seek justice.
السعي لتحقيق العدالة.
It's Qingmei! It's Lady Qingmei!
انها تشينغمي! إنها السيدة تشينغمي!
Lady Qingmei.
سيدة تشينغمي.
Lady Qingmei has arrived.
لقد وصلت السيدة تشينغمي.
♪I once fell into deep love♪
♪لقد وقعت في حب عميق ذات مرة♪
♪Caught in a drama of love and hate♪
♪وقعت في دراما الحب والكراهية♪
♪Trapped in self-made cages♪
♪محاصرون في أقفاص من صنعهم♪
♪To whom should I direct my questions♪
♪إلى من أوجه أسئلتي♪
♪Heal my wounds from past dreams♪
♪ شفاء جروحي من أحلام الماضي ♪
♪Fate bestowed me both joy and pain♪
♪لقد منحني القدر كل من الفرح والألم♪
♪Left me a kiss of love and hate♪
♪ترك لي قبلة من الحب والكراهية♪
♪Who will unravel my dreams so deep♪
♪من سيكشف أحلامي العميقة؟♪
♪Who will save me from this lonely place♪
♪من سينقذني من هذا المكان الوحيد♪
♪Who will give me back my lonely grace♪
♪من سيعيد لي نعمتي الوحيدة♪
♪I dare not ask the infatuated ones♪
♪لا أجرؤ على سؤال المغرمين♪
♪As the moonlight thickens♪
♪مع ازدياد كثافة ضوء القمر♪
♪What I await♪
♪ما أنتظره♪
♪Which heartless soul♪
♪أي روح بلا قلب♪
♪Love departs, hatred persists♪
♪الحب يرحل، والكراهية تبقى♪
♪I woke too soon to bygone bonds♪
♪استيقظت مبكرًا جدًا على الروابط القديمة♪
♪Forgetting the lost one in old dreams♪
♪نسيان المفقود في الأحلام القديمة♪
♪No longer waiting for estranged souls♪
♪لم يعد هناك انتظار للأرواح المنفصلة♪
♪Memories flow in the deep night♪
♪تتدفق الذكريات في الليل العميق♪
♪Illuminating lonely spirits♪
♪إضاءة الأرواح الوحيدة♪
♪Become an ordinary mortal♪
♪أصبح إنسانًا عاديًا♪
♪Next spring will open heart's doors♪
♪الربيع القادم سيفتح أبواب القلب♪
♪Not seeking a specific beloved♪
♪لا أبحث عن حبيب محدد♪
♪Gracefully embracing affections♪
♪احتضان المشاعر برشاقة♪